[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Bhola Cyclone of 1970 destroyed much of Pakistan.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This is a delicacy made from certain species of fish eggs, most notably the sturgeon.", "correct_answer": "Caviar", "incorrect_answers": ["Blintz", "Coffee", "Baklava"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This spirit is distilled from a fermented mash containing no less than 51% corn or maize in addition to wheat, rye and malted barley.", "correct_answer": "Bourbon", "incorrect_answers": ["Scotch", "Welsh whiskey", "Canadian whisky"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "If your cell phone runs out of power, this gadget will come to the rescue. Just plug it into your mobile phones charging port and turn the crank.", "correct_answer": "SOS Charger", "incorrect_answers": ["Manual Cranker Battery", "New Cell Phone", "Lithium Battery Generator"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these is a name of a location in the Lord of the Rings films that translates Pass of the Spider?", "correct_answer": "Cirith Ungol", "incorrect_answers": ["N\u00famenor", "Minas Morgul", "Minas Tirith"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the pet animal that Glenn Closes deranged character cooks in the 1987 movie Fatal Attraction?", "correct_answer": "Rabbit", "incorrect_answers": ["Turtle", "Cat", "Parrot"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following foods is poorest in carbohydrates?", "correct_answer": "Pork", "incorrect_answers": ["Cheese", "Potatoes", "Milk"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following terms refers to the fear of being buried alive?", "correct_answer": "Taphephobia", "incorrect_answers": ["Gephyrophobia", "Phagophobia", "Mysophobia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Where does the word Rastafarian come from?", "correct_answer": "The real name of a king", "incorrect_answers": ["It comes from a Taino name", "The name of a song", "It means the good religion"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The main purpose of the observatory located on the north shore of Big Bear Lake in the San Bernardino Mountains, California is studying what?", "correct_answer": "The Sun", "incorrect_answers": ["Pulsars", "Black holes", "The Moon"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This cocktail is a sweet combination of 4 oz. vodka, 2 oz. Midori and some Sprite mixed with ice.", "correct_answer": "Midori Dream", "incorrect_answers": ["Hocus Pocus", "Hole In One", "Highland Sling"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the ultra-popular Rambo franchise it is not unusual for Rambo to go about his killing with a little help from a friend. In which film would you find Rambo getting help from School Boy?", "correct_answer": "Rambo", "incorrect_answers": ["Rambo III", "First Blood Part II", "First Blood"]}]